[
  {
    "id": "T7D01",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which instrument would you use to measure electric potential?",
    "answers": [
      "An ammeter",
      "A voltmeter",
      "A wavemeter",
      "An ohmmeter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D02",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "How is a voltmeter connected to a component to measure applied voltage?",
    "answers": [
      "In series",
      "In parallel",
      "In quadrature",
      "In phase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D03",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "When configured to measure current, how is a multimeter connected to a component?",
    "answers": [
      "In series",
      "In parallel",
      "In quadrature",
      "In phase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D04",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which instrument is used to measure electric current?",
    "answers": [
      "An ohmmeter",
      "An electrometer",
      "A voltmeter",
      "An ammeter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D06",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following can damage a multimeter?",
    "answers": [
      "Attempting to measure resistance using the voltage setting",
      "Failing to connect one of the probes to ground",
      "Attempting to measure voltage when using the resistance setting",
      "Not allowing it to warm up properly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D07",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following measurements are made using a multimeter?",
    "answers": [
      "Signal strength and noise",
      "Impedance and reactance",
      "Voltage and resistance",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D08",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following types of solder should not be used for radio and electronic applications?",
    "answers": [
      "Acid-core solder",
      "Lead-tin solder",
      "Rosin-core solder",
      "Tin-copper solder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D09",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is the characteristic appearance of a cold tin-lead solder joint?",
    "answers": [
      "Dark black spots",
      "A bright or shiny surface",
      "A rough or lumpy surface",
      "Excessive solder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D10",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What reading indicates that an ohmmeter is connected across a large, discharged capacitor?",
    "answers": [
      "Increasing resistance with time",
      "Decreasing resistance with time",
      "Steady full-scale reading",
      "Alternating between open and short circuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7D11",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following precautions should be taken when measuring in-circuit resistance with an ohmmeter?",
    "answers": [
      "Ensure that the applied voltages are correct",
      "Ensure that the circuit is not powered",
      "Ensure that the circuit is grounded",
      "Ensure that the circuit is operating at the correct frequency"
    ]
  }
]